

Personal Information

Name: Kiattikul Singsuriya (เกียรติกุล สิงห์สุริยะ)

Age: 26 years old. Family Status: Single Nationality: Thai

Date of Birth: 30th October 1989.

Military Status: Exempted.

Address: No.147/41 Moo 4, The Privacy Rewadee, Building A, Talat Khwan,

Mueang Nonthaburi, Nonthaburi 11000.

Tel: 092-3744446

E-mail: kiattikul.sing@gmail.com

Linked in : th.linkedin.com/in/kiattikul



Summary

I am a proficient developer with 3 years. Concentrating on Java and J2EE for the past 4 years, I have extensive of using open source and libraries to implement enterprise class application. I am also a keen proponent of agile methodologies and have successfully introduced agile techniques into project which I have managed. I am seeking a challenging position as a programmer, ideally in a project team developing large scale enterprise system.



Education

- B.Sc. in Information Technology, Maejo University, THA, 2008-2012.
- Studying M.Sc. in Web Engineering, Dhurakij Pundit University, THA, 2014-Present.



Certificates

- Information Technology Passport Examination (IP) License THIP14A0012
 Information Technology Professional Examination Council (ITPEC) November 2014 Present.
- Dhamma Scholar Advanced Level. *License ซม* 3350/0047

 Central Dharma Testing Service Headquarters of Thailand December 2007 Present.

ጰ

Skills & Expertise

- Knowledge of Programming in Java, C#, Object C and C++ language.
- Knowledge of Mobile Development (Android Application).
- Knowledge of creating software test plan.
- Knowledge of System analysis and design with UML.
- Knowledge of Object Oriented Programming.
- Knowledge of PL/SQL.
- Understanding of development on MVC model.
- Open source libraries (Struts1, Struts2, JSF, Seam, Jboss tools, Spring, Prime face and Jakarta POI).
- Web / Application Servers (Apache, Tomcat).
- Database Servers (Oracle, MySQL).
- Spoken, Listening and written English fairly.



Client Experiences

Programmer Analyst at Advanced System Consulting Co.,Ltd. (2 Year 6 Months)

Duration: November 2015 – Present (3 months) Outsource on PTT ICT Solutions Company Limited.

Duration: May 2014 – November 2015 (1 year 6 months) Outsource on Advanced Info Service PCL.

Duration: November 2013 - May 2014 (7 months) Outsource on True Information Technology Co., Ltd

Programmer Analyst at Infinite Computing System (Thailand) Co.,Ltd. (7 Months)

Duration: May 2013 - November 2013 (7 months) Outsource on Advanced Info Service PCL.

Programmer at Command Control Technology Co.,Ltd. (1 Year)

Duration: May 2012 - April 2013 (1 year)



Project Experiences

• Report BOT (Report for Bank of Thailand)

Duration: November 2015 – Present

Industry: PTT ICT Solutions Company Limited
Team: ATA (Technology & Analytic Applications)

Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities:

Responsible for Developing Programs Report BOT (Report for Bank of Thailand) such as: Report Providing electronic money (e-Money), Report Spending on electronic money (e-Money) by the valued, Payment Problem and Back-end balance was calculated by months. Reporting module has been designed and implemented by Jakarta POI. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Spring framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database to Oracle.

• Report Redesign

Duration: August 2015 – November 2015 **Industry**: Advanced Info Service Plc.

Team: SAND (eService)

Position: Programmer Analyst (Business intelligence)

Responsibilities:

o Responsible for Developing Programs Report Redesign (Analysis of data from the marketing team) request by Marketing AIS. Report Develop tools used Tableau; Server database Oracle Server.

LOG SSB(Service Sync Batch)

Duration: March 2015 - July 2015 **Industry**: Advanced Info Service Plc.

Team: SAND (eService)

Position: Programmer Analyst (PL/SQL Developer)

Responsibilities:

o Responsible for Developing Programs Log SSB (Service Sync Batch file log) request by eService Team. Log Batch Develop tools used PL/SQL a back-end solution; Server database Oracle Server.

SSO (Single Sign on):

Duration: December 2014 - February 2015

Industry: Advanced Info Service Plc.

Team: SAND (SSO)

Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities:

 Responsible for Developing programs SSO (Jobs Sync Update data Support Mobile Application) request by SSO Team. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Develop tools used as SSIS (SQL Server Integration Services) a back-end solution; Server database MySQL Server.

Access Matrix:

Duration: October 2014 – January 2015 Industry: Advanced Info Service Plc. Team: SAND (Project Access Matrix) Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities:

Responsible for Developing programs Access Matrix (Access Control and Identity Management)
request by Staff AIS. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Spring
MVC framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database Oracle.

• CDR Internal BOS:

Duration: May 2013 – October 2013, May 2014 – August 2014

Industry: Advanced Info Service Plc.

Team: IRB (BOSD)

Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities:

 Responsible for Developing programs CDR Internal BOS (Call Detail Rating Internal for Billing Online System) requested by AIS Call Center. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Spring MVC framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database to Web Services for BOS.

• 3C : (Convergent Customer Care)

Duration: November 2013 – Present

Industry: True Information Technology Co., Ltd.

Team: 3C

Position: Programmer Analyst

Responsibilities:

 Responsible for Developing programs CCC (Convergent Customer Care) Project requested by True Call Center. The System has been designed following common MVC pattern: Prime Faces framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database to Web Service for OM Team and CCB-INT Team. APP:

Duration: March 2013 – April 2013

Industry: Command Control Technology Co. Ltd.

Team: Web Application **Position**: Java Programmer

Responsibilities:

 Responsible for Developing programs APP such as: backlist module and what list module. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Struts2 framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database to Oracle.

• NSureX: http://www.nsurex.com/

Duration: August 2012 – April 2013

Industry: Command Control Technology Co. Ltd.

Team: Web Application **Position**: Java Programmer

Responsibilities:

Responsible for Developing programs NSureX such as: Login module, User module, Group user module, System configuration module, Dealer module and Dealer Child module; Reporting module has been designed and implemented by iReport and Jakarta POI. The system has been designed following common MVC pattern: Struts2 framework is being used as a front-end solution; Server database to Oracle.

• Valentine II(Magic library System):

Duration: June 2012 - April 2013

Industry: Command Control Technology Co. Ltd.

Team: Web Application **Position**: Java Programmer

Responsibilities:

 Responsible for support Developing Programs Valentine II. JSF JBoss framework; Server database to Oracle.